Guide to Bess Reed papers 1901-1984
Montana Historical Society Research Center
Bess Reed papers
1901-1984
Montana Historical Society, Research Center Archives Archives 225 N. Roberts PO Box 201201 Helena MT 59620-1201 (406) 444-2681 MHSlibrary@mt.gov
MC 336
Reed, Bess, 1892-1984
10 linear feet of shelf space
The collection consists of material from former Republican state legislator Bess Reed from Missoula, Montana who served in the Montana Assembly from 1951-1953, 1961. Included are correspondence and subject files (1945-1982) on many issues with which Reed was prominently involved including School Foundation Program for public education, water pollution control, extension of Social Security to public employees, and gender equity. There are also extensive files pertaining to Reed’s involvement in local political organizations such as the Montana Federation of Business and Professional Women's Club, Missoula County Republican Club, Montana Federation of Republican Women's Club, Montana Young Republicans, Parent-Teacher Organization, School Board Association, Missoula Chamber of Commerce, Montana Health Planning Council, Missoula City Hall Planning Committee, Council on Aging, Montana Society for Crippled Children, Montana Story Project, Sojourners Club of Missoula, Soroptimist Club of Missoula, and United Way.
Biographical Note
Republican state legislator and a member of the Missoula School District 1 Board of Trustees for 21 years was born in Montgomery, Minnesota, on October 15, 1892. She attended Valley City Teachers College in Valley City, North Dakota, in Domestic Science. On graduation Bess taught school for six years; four years in North Dakota and was principal at Stanford Montana and then on to teach high school chemistry in St. Maries Idaho. When it became evident that her teaching salary was not enough to support herself she decided to give up teaching and went to work for the Milwaukee Road. She worked for the railroad in St. Maries and Spokane, Washington for the next six years. On November 9, 1925 she married Dr. Dallas J. Reed and moved to Missoula shortly thereafter. The couple had one son, Dallas J. Reed, Jr.
From the time Bess arrived in Missoula in 1925, she was committed to public affairs. She led local and state chapters of the PTA (Parent Teachers Association). Bess was the secretary of the Montana Society for Crippled Children for eight years, and Missoula County's Girls State Chairwomen for 19 years. For 17 years she was the executive secretary of the Community Chest (the United Way predecessor) and served on the Board of Directors of the Missoula Chamber of Commerce. As a member of the Missoula Business and Professional Women's Club she was voted Women of the Year in 1952 and was their State President in 1964 and in 1976 was their Women in History in their Statewide Bi-Centennial book. On March 27, 1971, the Missoula Chamber of Commerce declared Bess Reed Day. Altogether Bess worked for the city of Missoula for 52 years.
In her four years in the Legislature 1951-1953 and 1961, Bess took a particular interest in education and health and was an active proponent of the Equal Rights Amendment. She was chairwomen of Education and Public Health, Morals and Safety Committee, Mines and Mining, State Boards and Institutions, Ways and Means, Banking and Insurance, and Conservation and Development. Lands.
Bess Reed died at the age of 91 in Missoula, Montana on June 4, 1984.
Dr. Dallas J. Reed, Missoula chiropractor, was born in Butte, Montana on April 16, 1891. He was employed by the Milwaukee Railroad in 1907 where he worked as a timekeeper. He remained with the railroad company until 1917, when he enlisted in Spokane, Washington and was sent to France. He was first stationed in a French headquarters office, and then saw action with the second division at Chateau Thierry, Belleau Wood and Soissons. In Soissons he was wounded just after going over the top, and was only one of 28 survivors of his company of 238 men. He returned to his employment with the Milwaukee Road in 1919, remaining in the work until 1921, when he entered the National College of Chiropractic in Chicago. After his graduation in 1924, he practiced in Whitehall, Montana for a year, moving to Missoula in 1925. He died on April 29, 1944 after a long illness.
The collection documents Bess Reed’s career as a member of the Montana Assembly and her involvement in Missoula community organizations. The collection is organized into 8 series:
Series 1: The bulk of the Personal files series contain material from the period 1940-1980, related to Bess Reed’s political and social life. These files include biographical information, diaries, legal documents, research notes, school notes and records, speeches, writings, and newspaper clippings. Included are correspondence materials covering the period 1913 to 1981. Correspondence include family; Ann Allison (Coordinator of Women's Activities); Governor and Mrs. Tim Babcock; Stella E. Barker (Polk County Recorder); Ronald Reagan; Richard Simpson (Chairman of the Republican Congressional Committee); and Kay Thompson (President Missoula Business and Professional Women's Club). Newspaper clippings, which date from the 1940s through the 1980s, specifically focus on Bess Reed and her social and political involvements.
Series 2: The bulk of the Legislative files contain material from 1948-1961. This series documents Reed’s service while a member of the Montana Assembly. The series includes correspondence; subject files on education, domestic relationships, Indian affairs and equal rights; campaign leaflets; drawings of state legislators; and a list of the Republican members.
Series 3-7: These series contain records from 1942-1982 that document Bess Reed’s involvement in community political organizations. The files contain correspondence, board minutes, financial records, speeches, subject files, and printed material of the Montana Federation of Business and Professional Women’s Club, Missoula County Republican club, Montana Federation of Republican Women’s Club, Montana Young Republicans, Montana Republican Club, Parent-Teacher Organization, School Board Association, Missoula Chamber of Commerce, Montana Health Planning Council, Missoula City Hall Planning Committee, Montana Society for Crippled Children, Montana Story Project, Sojourners Club of Missoula, Soroptimist Club of Missoula, and United Way.
Series 8: The bulk of the Dallas Reed, Sr. files contains material about the period 1901 to 1945. The files include Reed’s World War I enrollment papers and general correspondence from the United States Veterans’ Bureau and the Veterans’ Welfare Commission. Also included are correspondence about Reed’s death and his application to attend the National College of Chiropractic in Chicago.
Arranged by series
Collection is open for research
Acquisition information available upon request.
Artifacts, photographs, and printed materials have been separated to the Museum, Photo Archives, and Library respectively.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the Montana Historical Society Archives catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search under these terms.
Montana Federation of Business and Professional Women's Club--History; Republican Party (Mont.)
Community organizations--Montana--Missoula.; Education--Montana--Missoula.; Equal rights amendments--Montana.; Health--Law and Legislation--Montana.; Legislators--Montana--Missoula.; Parents' and teachers' association--Montana-- Missoula--History.; School boards--Montana--Missoula--History.; World War, 1914-1918--Documents.
Missoula (Mont.)--Politics and government.; Montana--Politics and government.
Montana
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Personal Papers
  - Biographical Materials
    - Biographical writings (probably by Bess Reed), 1942-1945, 1964, undated (Box-folder 1 / 1)
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - A-C (correspondents include Ann Allison (Coordinator of Women's Activities); Dean Aman; Governor and Mrs. Tim Babcock; Stella E. Barker (Polk County Recorder); Lyndell Bell; and Ruth C. Cullin), 1950-1977 (Box-folder 1 / 2)
    - D-F (correspondents include Margaret Daems; Wesley D'Ewart; M. J. Dowling; John J. Burke; Elizabeth Connelly; J. W. Emmert; Margaret Clifford; and Ruby Froebel (President of the Legion Auxiliary), 1913, 1953-1981 (Box-folder 1 / 3)
    - Family (correspondents include Dallas J. Reed; Dallas J. Reed Jr.; Joyce Reed; Pamela Reed; William Riggert; and Franklin Robbie), 1946-1982 (Box-folder 1 / 4)
    - G-H (correspondents include Earle N. Genzberger; Fred Heinecke; John H. Hoppe; and Mark Hatfield), 1926, 1953-1966 (Box-folder 1 / 5)
    - I-M (correspondents include Helen G. Irwin; Colonel Erwin T. Koch; George Krava; William R. Mackay; and Mike Mansfield), 1942-1971 (Box-folder 1 / 6)
    - N-P (correspondents include H. K. Newburn; (President Montana State University); Serge Obolensky (President of the Ambassador Hotel); and Don Pettit), 1944-1978 (Box-folder 1 / 7)
    - R-V (correspondents include Ronald Reagan; Richard Simpson (Chairman of the Republican Congressional Committee); Frances Sanborn; Edna Wilma Sharp; Charles Staples; Clara Tanner; Kay Thompson (President Missoula Business and Professional Women's Club); and Robert Venafro), 1953-1981 (Box-folder 1 / 8)
    - W-Z (correspondents include Besty Wilcox; Tomme Lu Worden; and Mrs. Reuben Zieg), 1961, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 9)
  - Outgoing Correspondence
    - D-V (correspondents include Otto Habadank; Margate Kienst; Dallas J. Reed Jr.; and Robert Venefro), 1949-1979 (Box-folder 1 / 10)
  - General Correspondence
    - Letters to Mora from Edward, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 1 / 11)
  - Court Papers
    - Bess Reed Estate Papers, 1984 (Box-folder 1 / 12)
    - Fred J. Rocek Estate Papers, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 1 / 13)
  - Diaries
    - Journal Writings, 1946-1949 (Box-folder 1 / 14)
    - Religious Journal Writings, 1934-1935, undated (Box-folder 1 / 15-16)
  - Financial Records
    - Receipts (sampled), 1950-1970, 1984 (Box-folder 1 / 17)
    - Renters Information on the Farm, 1937-1938, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 1 / 18)
    - Stock Certificates, 1924, 1930 (Box-folder 1 / 19)
  - Legal Documents
    - Contracts, 1946 (Box-folder 1 / 20)
    - Contracts; Farming, 1950-1970, 1984 (Box-folder 1 / 21)
    - Farm Property and Foreclosure, Minnesota (includes correspondence), 1926-1941, 1949 (Box-folder 2 / 1)
  - Membership Records
    - Fraternities, 1947, 1961, undated (Box-folder 2 / 2)
  - Printed Material
    - "Meet the Man Who Plans to Rule America", 1958 (Box-folder 2 / 3)
    - "Public High School Education in Missoula, 1884-1955", 1970 (Box-folder 2 / 4)
    - "Supervisors of Elementary Education", 1953 (Box-folder 2 / 5)
    - World's Woman's Christian Temperance Union, undated (Box-folder 2 / 6)
  - Research Notes
    - A-Z (re Alder, Mortimer J.; Bailey, Hannah; Beales, A.C.F.; Burritt, Elihu; DuBois, W.E.B.; Earhart, Mary; Education; Featherstone, H.A.; Gooch, G.P.; Hemlaben, Sylvester; Henry, Patrick; Ladd, William; Parkman, Mary; Patterson, Ernest Minor; religion and peace; Wynner, Edith; and Ziff, William), undated (Box card file box 1)
    - Bailey, Hannah J. (for additional notes on Hannah Bailey see card file box 1), undated (Box-folder 2 / 7)
    - Religion and Peace (for additional notes on religion and peace see card file box 1), undated (Box-folder 2 / 8)
    - Willard, Frances, undated (Box-folder 2 / 9)
  - School Notes and Records
    - Report Cards, 1911-1913, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 2 / 10)
    - School Certificates and Programs (Oversize Material: see map case), 1911-1913, 1917-1918 (Box-folder 2 / 11)
  - Speeches
    - "Education in Missoula", 1954 (Box-folder 2 / 12)
    - "Faith of our Fathers", 1959 (Box-folder 2 / 13)
    - "Status of Women", 1961 (Box-folder 2 / 14)
    - Woman of the Year, 1958 (Box-folder 2 / 15)
  - Subject Files
    - Bess Reed Memorial Foundation, undated (Box-folder 2 / 16)
    - City of Missoula Purchase of Bess Reed's Home, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 2 / 17)
    - Mother of the Year, 1974, 1979 (Box-folder 2 / 18)
    - Religion, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 2 / 19)
    - Women as Professionals, 1952 (Box-folder 2 / 20)
    - Women in Political Positions, 1951 (Box-folder 2 / 21)
  - Writings
    - "Humblest Hour", undated (Box-folder 2 / 22)
    - "Montana Health Planning Council", 1959 (Box-folder 2 / 23)
    - Religious writings; "The Chide of the New Order", 1935 (Box-folder 2 / 24)
    - Religious writings; "Meditation", 1934 (Box-folder 2 / 25)
    - Religious writings; unidentified, 1941, undated (Box-folder 3 / 1)
  - Miscellany
    - Awards, 1950, 1961-1983, 1987, undated (Box-folder 3 / 2-4)
    - Date books, 1949, 1953, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 3 / 5)
    - Guest Book (Bess Reed Day), 1971 (Box-folder 3 / 6-7)
    - Guest Book ("From Her Friends in Education"), undated (Box-folder OVBX / 1)
    - Hellgate Centennial; Hellgate Holidays, undated (Box-folder 3 / 8)
    - Invitations, 1950-1971, 1975, 1977 (Box-folder 3 / 9)
    - Membership Cards (sampled), 1960-1961, 1966, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 3 / 10)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 3 / 11)
    - Notes; Education, 1973 (Box-folder 3 / 12)
    - Notes; Unidentified, undated (Box-folder 4 / 1)
    - Scrapbook (Among Her Activities), 1965-1970 (Box-folder 4 / 2-4)
    - Scrapbook (Bess Reed Day), 1971 (Box-folder 4 / 5-7)
    - Scrapbook (re family and involvement in local political organization), 1947-1971 (Box-folder 4 / 8)
    - Scrapbooks (re legislative campaign; Dallas J. Reed Jr. military service; personal greetings; and involvement in local political organizations), 1951-1960 (Box-folder OVBX / 2-5)
    - Teaching in White Sulphur Springs, 1961 (Box-folder 4 / 9)
  - Clippings
    - Miscellaneous (re legislative and organizational activities), 1942-1982, undated (Box-folder 5 / 1-6)
- Legislative Files
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - Miscellaneous Political Correspondence (re increasing the School Foundation Program for public education; Uniform Drug Act; Montana Narcotic laws; and Nurse Practice Act; Highway Committee; extension of Social Security to public employees; and regulation of chiropractors), 1948-1958 (Box-folder 6 / 1-5)
    - Miscellaneous Political Correspondence (re education and teacher standards; operation of public schools; regulating trading stamps; Physical Therapy Bill; licensing of Plumbers; Equal Rights amendment; and the unionization of the armed services), 1960-1984 (Box-folder 6 / 6-9)
  - Outgoing Correspondence
    - Miscellaneous Political Correspondence (re addition to Glacier National park; teacher retirement; School Foundation Program; water pollution control; trading stamps; sale of beer in grocery store; and the sale of comic books), 1945-1982, undated (Box-folder 6 / 10)
  - Financial Records
    - Account Book; Victory Exchange, 1942-1944 (Box-folder 6 / 11)
    - Legislative Budgets, 1952-1963 (Box-folder 6 / 12)
  - Legal Documents
    - Contracts; Political Radio Broadcast, 1962, 1964 (Box-folder 6 / 13)
  - Printed Material
    - "Here's How it Works: An Explanation of Montana's Equalization Foundation Program", 1960 (Box-folder 6 / 14)
  - Speeches
    - To Committee on Education, 1946 (Box-folder 7 / 1)
  - Subject Files
    - Domestic Relations, 1963 (Box-folder 7 / 2)
    - Education (re public school finances; School Foundation Program; and higher education in Montana), 1950-1951, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 7 / 3)
    - Equal Rights, 1953, 1958, undated (Box-folder 7 / 4)
    - Indian Affairs, undated (Box-folder 7 / 5)
    - Legislative Bills (re HB 347 defining obscene literature and so-called comic books; HB 388 providing penalties for violating the narcotic drug act; resolution supporting the Mayor's declaration honoring Bess Reed; SB 110 school funding; and HB 127 School Foundation Program), 1961, 1982, undated (Box-folder 7 / 6)
    - Public Land Conservation, 1959, undated (Box-folder 7 / 7)
    - State Lands, undated (Box-folder 7 / 8)
    - Teenage Pregnancy, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 7 / 9)
  - Miscellany
    - Campaign Leaflets, undated (Box-folder 7 / 10)
    - Caricatures of Legislators (by James M. Haughey), 1953, 1955 (Box-folder 7 / 11)
    - Certificates of Appointment, 1952, 1954-1955, 1960 (Box-folder 7 / 12)
    - Missoula County Contributors, 1963 (Box-folder 7 / 13)
    - Montana Legislature (includes seating charts; list of House and Senate members; list of lobbyists; parliamentary table; and order of business), 1954-1955, 1960 (Box-folder 7 / 14)
    - Notes (includes legislative and campaign notes), 1960-1963 (Box-folder 7 / 15)
- Montana Federation of Business and Professional Women's Club
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - Regarding Organizational Activities, 1948-1976, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 7 / 16-19)
  - Outgoing Correspondence
    - Regarding Organizational Activities, 1953-1955, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 7 / 20-21)
  - General Correspondence
    - Regarding Organizational Activities, 1953, 1955, 1969 (Box-folder 7 / 22)
  - Organizational Records
    - By-Laws, 1959-1967, 1972, undated (Box-folder 8 / 1)
    - Budget and Membership Report, 1967 (Box-folder 8 / 2)
    - Conference and Convention Files, 1953-1955, 1966-1967, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 8 / 3-4)
    - Duties of District Director, undated (Box-folder 8 / 5)
    - Installation of Officers, 1943, 1961 (Box-folder 8 / 6)
    - Minutes; Executive Committee, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 8 / 7)
    - Programs and Yearbooks, 1929-1930, 1952-1955 (Box-folder 8 / 8)
  - Printed Material
    - Handbook of Federation Proceedings, 1956, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 8 / 9)
  - Speeches
    - "Emblem Ceremony", 1962 (Box-folder 8 / 10)
    - "Membership", undated (Box-folder 8 / 11)
    - To Business and Professional Women's Club Regional Convention, 1953 (Box-folder 8 / 12)
    - To Business and Professional Women's Club Thompson Falls, 1954 (Box-folder 8 / 13)
  - Miscellany
    - Bicentennial Project, undated (Box-folder 8 / 14)
    - Proclamation; 50th Anniversary, 1970 (Box-folder 8 / 15)
    - Spokane Champagne Bus Trip, undated (Box-folder 8 / 16)
    - Questionnaire, 1970, 1972 (Box-folder 8 / 17)
- Montana Republican Party Organizations
  - General Correspondence
    - Missoula County Republican Club (re activities), 1961, 1963 (Box-folder 8 / 18)
    - Montana Federation of Republican Women's Club (re activities), 1958, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 8 / 19)
    - Montana Young Republicans (re activities), 1961 (Box-folder 8 / 20)
  - Organizational Records
    - By-Laws and Membership Reports; Missoula Republican Women's Club, 1947, 1951, 1958-1962 (Box-folder 8 / 21)
    - By-Laws and Membership Reports; Montana Federation of Republican Women's Club, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 8 / 22)
    - Minutes; Montana Federation of Republican Women's Club, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 8 / 23)
    - Platform and Resolutions; Montana Republican Party, 1958, 1960 (Box-folder 9 / 1)
  - Printed Material
    - "Missoula County Republican Club" (newsletter), 1960-1963 (Box-folder 9 / 2)
    - "Montana Young Republican" (newsletter), 1961 (Box-folder 9 / 3)
    - "National Federation of Republican Women" (newsletter), 1961 (Box-folder 9 / 4)
    - "Why Am I A Republican?", 1951 (Box-folder 9 / 5)
  - Speeches
    - To Missoula County Republican Women's Club, undated (Box-folder 9 / 6)
- Parent-Teacher Organization
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - Regarding Organizational Activities, 1945-1982 (Box-folder 9 / 7-10)
  - General Correspondence
    - Regarding Organizational Activities, 1948-1953, 1959 (Box-folder 9 / 11)
  - Organizational Records
    - By-Laws and Parliamentary Procedures, 1945, undated (Box-folder 9 / 12)
    - Conventions, 1948, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 9 / 13)
    - Minutes, 1946, 1948, 1970, 1975 (Box-folder 9 / 14)
    - Report; "Curriculum in the Federal Way Elementary Schools", undated (Box-folder 9 / 15)
    - Workshop; Parent-Teacher Organization, 1945 (Box-folder 9 / 16)
    - Workshops-Conferences, 1947-1953 (Box-folder 9 / 17)
  - Speeches
    - "Future Teachers of America", undated (Box-folder 9 / 18)
    - To Whitehall P.T.A., 1956 (Box-folder 9 / 19)
  - Subject Files
    - Home-School Cooperative, 1945 (Box-folder 9 / 20)
    - Peabody Report (summary of main ideas at county conferences), undated (Box-folder 9 / 21)
  - Miscellany
    - Scrapbook (includes news clippings and notes), undated (Box-folder 9 / 22)
    - Resume of the Yellowstone National Park School Problem, 1948 (Box-folder 9 / 23)
- School Board Association
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - Regarding Organizational Activities, 1946-1978, 1981 (Box-folder 10 / 1-4)
  - Outgoing Correspondence
    - Regarding Organizational Activities, 1946-1963, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 10 / 5)
  - General Correspondence
    - Regarding Organizational Activities, 1949-1950, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 10 / 6)
  - Financial Records
    - Financial Reports, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 10 / 7)
  - Organization Records
    - Board Minutes, 1955, 1962 (Box-folder 10 / 8)
    - Constitution and Membership, 1957-1961, undated (Box-folder 10 / 9)
    - President's Message, 1961, 1964 (Box-folder 10 / 10)
    - Workshops, 1961, 1963 (Box-folder 10 / 11-12)
  - Printed Materials
    - "Local Boards of School Trustees in Montana: A Study of Selected Policies and Practices" (Report), 1962-1963 (Box-folder 10 / 13)
    - "School Board Members Opinion Relating to Federal Financial Assistance to Schools" (Report), 1962 (Box-folder 10 / 14)
  - Subject Files
    - Western Interstate School Board Association, 1955, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 10 / 15)
  - Miscellany
    - Certificate of Election (Missoula School District 1 Board of Trustee), 1950, 1953 (Box-folder 11 / 1)
    - Notes (re National Convention), undated (Box-folder 11 / 2)
    - Policy Statement on National Legislation, undated (Box-folder 11 / 3)
- Community Activities
  - General Correspondence
    - Missoula Chamber of Commerce (re activities), 1951-1981 (Box-folder 11 / 4)
    - Montana Health Planning Council (re activities), 1948, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 11 / 5)
  - Organizational Records
    - Minutes; Citizens Committee on Education, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 11 / 6)
    - Minutes; Missoula Community Council, 1970 (Box-folder 11 / 7)
    - Minutes; Montana Health Planning Council, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 11 / 8)
    - Minutes; Women's Club of Missoula, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 11 / 9)
  - Subject Files
    - American Legion Auxiliary, 1955, 1969-1970, 1973 (Box-folder 11 / 10)
    - American Legion Auxiliary; Montana Girls State, 1925, 1979, 1982 (Box-folder 11 / 11)
    - Children's Welfare; 80 et 40, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 11 / 12)
    - Council on Aging, 1958, 1960-1961, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 11 / 13)
    - Fort Missoula Historical Society, 1979 (Box-folder 11 / 14)
    - Eastern Star Training Awards for Religious Leadership, undated (Box-folder 11 / 15)
    - Home Service for the Elderly, 1959 (Box-folder 11 / 16)
    - Kiwanis Club, 1976, 1979 (Box-folder 11 / 17)
    - Missoula Bi-Centennial Celebration, 1976 (Box-folder 11 / 18)
    - Missoula City Hall Planning Committee, 1965 (Box-folder 11 / 19)
    - Missoula County Airport, 1970 (Box-folder 11 / 20)
    - Missoula Police Department, 1957, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 11 / 21)
    - Missoula Public Library, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 11 / 22)
    - Montana Society for Crippled Children, 1947-1955, 1966-1980 (Box-folder 11 / 23)
    - Montana Special Olympics; Missoula Chapter, 1980 (Box-folder 11 / 24)
    - Montana Story Project, 1964, 1975 (Box-folder 11 / 25)
    - Mount Jumbo School; Open House, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 11 / 26)
    - Sojourners Club of Missoula, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 11 / 27)
    - Soroptimist Club of Missoula, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 11 / 28)
    - United Way (Community Chest), 1973, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 11 / 29)
  - Miscellany
    - Notes, undated (Box-folder 11 / 30)
- Dallas Reed, Sr.